{
    "id": "44c4f55d5581437cbaca23c7beec6872",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is a question ............................................ nobody can answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9f749fe827cf49108db7f8e87baf8253"
        },
        {
            "question": "I stayed an extra night ............................................... I could see Merlin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such that",
                "so that",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f849b6e22874e70b457be7824d0a407"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................................................... I was having a shower, I slipped on the floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whereas",
                "Since",
                "While"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fe87acce18224af2845c8ad74eeb8517"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................................... she was too angry to speak, Alice said nothing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Because",
                "Since",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "540a73bfdbcf4eb388d9369b5c1b9ece"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................ the coat was expensive, I bought it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bc07e8e72a8e4d54a38d48fc1daf3fb4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The house ............................................... I live is very small.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7590dbfe2a54a30921e604d832646b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will always remember the day ................................................ I first met you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab7e2b0d96894cfa906a79cb192503f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got a friend ........................................... serves in the army.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ebb6975017dc49078e4700dced7ce38d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cook slowly ..................................................... it is ready.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8109c225f3574b3b8ff05a583c454338"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................... I will have time I am not sure at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whether",
                "Unless",
                "Weather"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "db4097e5e78046d0b360a4e65ac697cc"
        }
    ]
}